<DialogueTree xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/dialogue_schema.xsd">
	<NameField>Tuner</NameField>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name></Name>
		<EntryCondition>DEFAULT</EntryCondition>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Hello! Welcome to the Banjo Galaxy.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueTarget>1</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>1</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Green Base is lovely today, isn't it?</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Riebeck? What are you doing here?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>2</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Where are we?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>3</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Need help with your song?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>4</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>I have some fire lyrics for you!</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>6</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>I'll talk to you later!</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>5</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>
	
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>2</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Riebeck? You must be confusing me with someone else. I'm <![CDATA[<color=orange>Tuner</color>]]>.</Page>
			<Page>I'm an explorer from somewhere very far away. I came looking for inspiration to write a new song.</Page>
			<Page>I'm not really a musician, but I want to be.</Page>
			<Page>That's the tricky part about improving yourself... You have to always be seeking out new hobbies and skills.</Page>
			<Page>That's why I haven't stopped playing since we started talking. Hope it doesn't bother you.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueTarget>1</DialogueTarget>
		<RevealFacts>
			<FactID>TALK_TO_TUNER</FactID>
		</RevealFacts>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>3</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>You're currently standing in the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Lost Village</color>]]> on Green Base.</Page>
			<Page>Or that's my name for it, anyway. I thought it was fitting.</Page>
			<Page>Apparently this planet went through an ice age or two, and the previous tenants got sick of it and left. Well, most of them did anyway.</Page>
			<Page>I don't know much else than that. There's a lot of recordings scattered around that I can't translate. Perhaps you have <![CDATA[<color=orange>something that can translate them</color>]]>.</Page>
			<Page>It saddens me, though, to see the village abandoned like this. Imagine spending years building it, only to leave it all behind.</Page>
			<Page>Every creator's fear.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueTarget>1</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>4</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Yes! I'd love to have you help me with my song!</Page>
			<Page>I have the melody written already, so all I need are some fire <![CDATA[<color=orange>lyrics</color>]]>.</Page>
			<Page>In order to match the music, I need you to find <![CDATA[<color=orange>two verses with two lines apiece</color>]]>. Or just four lines.</Page>
			<Page>There are many interesting places to draw inspiration from across this galaxy. Try casting your net wide!</Page>
			<Page>Bring me the lyrics when you find them!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<RevealFacts>
			<FactID>TUNERS_REQUEST</FactID>
		</RevealFacts>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>5</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Have fun exploring the galaxy! Return here if you get worn out or want to chat.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

	<!-- The Lyric Input Part -->
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>6</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Did you find all of them?</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueTargetShipLogCondition>LOST_STRINGS_LYRICS</DialogueTargetShipLogCondition>
		<DialogueTargetShipLogCondition>LOST_VILLAGE_LYRICS</DialogueTargetShipLogCondition>
		<DialogueTargetShipLogCondition>DRIED_TEARS_RECORDER</DialogueTargetShipLogCondition>
		<DialogueTargetShipLogCondition>BRACKETS_REST_LYRIC</DialogueTargetShipLogCondition>
		<DialogueTarget>7</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>7</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>You did! Great! Let's try them out...</Page>
			<Page><![CDATA[<color=orange>At cost of time and life of friend, Our broken people I seek to amend.</color>]]></Page>
			<Page><![CDATA[<color=orange>Our world is buried under ice. The work I employ will never suffice.</color>]]></Page>
			<Page>...</Page>
			<Page>Well, that's interesting. That's not quite what I was looking for, but I'll take it.</Page>
			<Page>More importantly, I understand how you feel.</Page>
			<Page>Being an artist is scary. You are always at the risk of critisism and mockery.</Page>
			<Page>You pour your heart into your work and sometimes it doesn't amount to much, or you are beaten out by the better man in the end.</Page>
			<Page>However, that should never discourage you from discovering <![CDATA[<color=orange>who you are</color>]]>.</Page>
			<Page>And by helping me write this song, you have shown your desire for artistic expression. So thank you for that, friend.</Page>
			<Page>This isn't the last time you and I will cross paths. I'm sure we will see each other again.</Page>
			<Page>Don't <![CDATA[<color=orange>fret</color>]]> over it. ;)</Page>
			<Page>Speaking of <![CDATA[<color=orange>Fret</color>]]>, you should probably return to him to let him know what you've discovered.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<RevealFacts>
			<FactID>TUNERS_QUEST_COMPLETE</FactID>
		</RevealFacts>
	</DialogueNode>


</DialogueTree>