<DialogueTree xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/dialogue_schema.xsd">
	<NameField>Tuner</NameField>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name></Name>
		<EntryCondition>DEFAULT</EntryCondition>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Hello! Welcome to the Banjo Galaxy.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueTarget>1</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>1</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Green Base is lovely today, isn't it?</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Riebeck? What are you doing here?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>2</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Where are we?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>3</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Need help with your song?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>4</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>I'll talk to you later!</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>5</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>
	
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>2</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Riebeck? You must be confusing me with someone else. I'm <![CDATA[<color=orange>Tuner</color>]]>.</Page>
			<Page>I'm an explorer from somewhere very far away. I came looking for inspiration to write a new song.</Page>
			<Page>I'm not really a musician, but I want to be.</Page>
			<Page>That's the tricky part about improving yourself... You have to always be seeking out new hobbies and skills.</Page>
			<Page>That's why I haven't stopped playing since we started talking. Hope it doesn't bother you.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueTarget>1</DialogueTarget>
		<RevealFacts>
			<FactID>TALK_TO_TUNER</FactID>
		</RevealFacts>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>3</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>You're currently standing in the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Lost Village</color>]]> on Green Base.</Page>
			<Page>Or that's my name for it, anyway. I thought it was fitting.</Page>
			<Page>Apparently this planet went through an ice age or two, and the previous tenants got sick of it and left. Well, most of them did anyway.</Page>
			<Page>I don't know much else than that. There's a lot of recordings scattered around that I can't translate. Perhaps you have <![CDATA[<color=orange>something that can translate them</color>]]>.</Page>
			<Page>It saddens me, though, to see the village abandoned like this. Imagine spending years building it, only to leave it all behind.</Page>
			<Page>Every creator's fear.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueTarget>1</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>4</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Yes! I'd love to have you help me with my song!</Page>
			<Page>I have the melody written already, so all I need are some fire <![CDATA[<color=orange>lyrics</color>]]>.</Page>
			<Page>In order to match the music, I need you to find <![CDATA[<color=orange>two verses with two lines apiece</color>]]>. Or just four lines.</Page>
			<Page>There are many interesting places to draw inspiration from across this galaxy. Try casting your net wide.</Page>
			<Page>Come back to me when you get the lyrics!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<RevealFacts>
			<FactID>TUNERS_REQUEST</FactID>
		</RevealFacts>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>5</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Have fun exploring the galaxy! Return here if you get worn out or want to chat.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

	<!-- The Lyric Input Part -->

</DialogueTree>